Jhaal
Lut Hello friends, my name is Sachin and
today I have brought you a video, not a write-up.
So friends, today we are going to talk
about retail cyber insurance for such people. The demand for this insurance is
increasing in the market
because nowadays our studies have become online,
our office work has become online,
even our shopping has become online nowadays.
After Corona, many
services which used to be offline earlier, today all of them have also become
online.
What has happened with its arrival, friends, is that the
cyber world has grown a lot.
Earlier, there used to be one mobile smartphone in every house,
today there are four to five smartphones in every house.
Laptop computers used to be
in very few houses, today they are in almost every house.
So friends, what has happened is that
cyber crime is also
increasing here in the same way. People have got
space here, so in
what way can they continue committing cyber crime
and this is becoming very popular, friends, so
friends, in today's date, this policy is
needed for every family, so
friends, watch this video till the end so that
I will tell you that  Now you
can create this policy yourself within 2 to 3 minutes.
So friends, let's start this
video.
First of all, let's see
what has happened these days due to going online. Our
bank account information, our credit
card information, it easily reaches the
criminals. They
install some kind of software or in
some way extract our personal
information and misuse it. This causes
us huge
losses. You must have seen that nowadays a
web series came in the name of Tara,
which is only online and is
made on the skin only. Or many people you keep
seeing in the news that someone got
hacked and money was withdrawn from their account. So
friends, today this has become a very common thing.
If I am here, friends, Cyber ​​Crime
Robin is declaring our date for the
financial year 2221. He has told
that now our loss has increased to sixty-three crore rupees.
Loss means
friends, that this money has
not been returned at all.  The money was recovered
but the set and send method did
not come back in the financial year 20 and 21. So
friends,
I have
left you a scan of an article that was published in the Times of India here. Similarly, a
back article was published in Business Standard.
Here, the
officials of Microsoft India
say that cyber crime will cause economic loss up to
the Australian dollar worldwide by 2025.
So
friends, you can see
how much such big organizations are
concerned about cyber crime. In this way,
friends, let's move forward.
Another article was published in the Times of India on March 31,
2022. What happened here was that
an SBI application was
created and installed in people's mobile phones
and from their accounts, their
personal information, even their bank
account information was stolen and from here they suffered a lot of
financial loss. So see,
here they bring new methods of loans due to which
people are impressed here.  Yes,
and those who do not have much knowledge about cyber, those who do
not know
about it, they have to bear a lot of loss here, so
not only final, here they have to suffer a lot of mental loss,
I would say that mental loss is
also a lot, so friends,
first of all let us talk about the benefits of Spain, so
friends, the
first option that comes here is Identity
Depth, so here if suppose someone has
misused your body, then suppose
someone might have taken out your Aadhar card,
PAN card or some other passport information
and using these documents they might have
applied for a loan online, like suppose
here, and there are many such
websites which
give loans on uploading your documents, so here it is possible that
something has been done which is with your knowledge or
not with your consent, then you can suffer a
lot of loss here, so
friends, to compensate for such loss, this will
work on a mixture, your number two comes
according to the transaction, friends, without
your content, here suppose
from your bank account  If money was withdrawn
from your wallet, money was withdrawn from a mobile wallet
or your credit card
was misused online, then friends, the
loss for that too will be compensated for you,
but it should not happen that you received an OTP
on your mobile and you gave it to someone on their request, then
giving an OTP is
not a transaction as per this because you
yourself have given that OTP to someone of your own free will. Let's
talk about Cyber ​​Act Roshan, friends, first of all
understand Cyber ​​Act Roshan, is he a giver?
If you consider here, Cyber ​​Act
Roshan, on one hand, sending related
returns, if he is threatening the owners
here and some such messages are being sent so that he
can extort money, he is
asking for money from you, he is blackmailing you here, in a
way, whatever
expenses there are here, IT space will be used to burn that monkey,
or suppose someone has taken your data,
hacked the data, then for its restoration,
whatever investigation will be done here, then
all the money for that will be
given here. Let's talk about Malviya, friends,
here  So, Malviya is a kind of
software that is installed in your computer or
mobile phone
and keeps spying on all your
personal information and data. This
software can cause
you huge losses. I've even seen
many times when your device gets locked
and they demand money to unlock it. So,
friends, any losses you incur due to this method, whether to
recover that data
or to lose any other function, will be
covered here.
Friends, when cybercrime occurs, there are
many people who
demand money, or they
hack your social media account, or
your Facebook or Instagram, and
they may damage your reputation. They may
send messages to strangers from your account, or they may
send messages to your boss, and you may
even lose your job because of it. So, are there any
such losses due to this method, are they legal?
You have to clear the cost to get your job
back or if
you have to take any legal action against that person, then all the
expenses incurred in this way will be presented to you here. Let's move ahead
friends, here now let's
talk about cyber bullying. Cyber
bullying is also a type of cyber crime
friends, but here also it is similar that
suppose someone is sending messages from your mobile,
someone is being harassed through
those messages or it is possible that
threatening messages are sent from your mobile to someone like this
or to any of your close ones or because of this you may lose
your job or you may
even get arrested, even then here whatever you want, whether it is a
hunger strike or you need legal services, a
lawyer or an IT specialist
or you will
need a psychologist, friends, all the
losses that occur here in this way,
financial losses, will be covered here
and the legal fees will be charged,
if you have been mentally harassed and have to go to a
psychiatrist, then
whatever fees will be borne by you here also.
Whatever expenses will be incurred will be
presented here as well as the legal expenses in this, that is,
whatever legal consultation is required in all the options that I have told you so far, then
all the legal expenses will be given to you there.
If suppose any third party has
imposed any validations on you here
or if any loss is caused by the third party, then the
charges for that will also be seen here and
talking about the data restoration course, friends, suppose
your device has been locked
or faxed, that is,
according to the data and whatever that data is, it will be
required for recovery.
Your data has been locked by Malviya or
you have been booked under the Cyber ​​Act, then
whatever will be the charge for bringing back that data,
whatever forensic team
works on it or cyber experts work, then
charges are given for that too here.
Talking about forensic investigation, friends, the
forensic cost for up to 30 days will be covered here.
These are very experts in
forensic and this  Let's find out
who has committed cybercrime against you,
who is behind this, who is trying to harm you,
so whatever
sports work you do for 30 days, its expenses will be
shown here. Now friends, let's talk
about sequential losses.
Friends, these losses are such that
suppose money was withdrawn from your bank account, maybe
you were going to write it the next day
or you had to make your credit card
payment or you had to pay money to the bank for some other reason, then
here any
such losses have happened due to which
you have suffered further loss directly or
indirectly, so like there is a
brother-sister, then what is there is that
whatever charges you have incurred for the plan or
late payment fees or additional
interest on it, then whatever such Shukracharyas are there,
they will be presented here. Friends,
here I will also tell you a little about the airplane,
about the plan features, I will
explain to you in a little detail
that this line here is
not a prank for any one family member.  Here,
if you take this plan, it will work for four family members,
meaning if you have
taken the plan, then your wife will
work for it along with you, it will work for two children
and if you do not have children, meaning you are
husband and wife, then it will
work for your parents as well, if you are individuals and
not married, then it will work for your parents only,
provided that all four of these
three people should live at the same address
and if it happens that suppose
someone has gone out or someone is
out for studies within India
and there is a loss with them and their
address proof is of the same location
where the policy was purchased, then also
they will get that cover there, if we
talk about movie access, friends,
what is play access, it is nil here, Play
Services means that for any of the owner's accounts, if the
owner takes one lakh or two
lakh, then every insurance
company deducts claim access, that is, 5000 or
10,000  After that, after deducting the amount, you will be given the
money. So, there is nothing like that here. There are
messages coming out here. Whatever actual
claim comes here, it will be packed for you.
What are the colors of this device?
Friends, all the digital devices
are covered here like computers, laptops,
mobile phones, tablets, so
here any of this type of devices is
covered through these devices. If you
talk about the waiting period,
friends, there is no such waiting period here.
Your cover will start from the day you purchase your policy. There is
no such waiting period of six digits here
that if we talk about bus stand, friends, here the
company says that we will help you 24*7.
You can
call our hotline
and
we will support you in whatever way we can help you. So, if we
talk about submission here,
friends, like I told you, what kind of
things are you Malviya?  If cyber bullying happens, then
here there are some
sub-limits on some things, suppose
you have taken 5 lakhs, then we will
give you 50,000 on that, 1 lakh on that, it is different,
so I will give you the brochure, here in the
download link, in the description,
click on the
sub-limit, it will appear, otherwise when you
purchase this plan, there is also a buy
option, click on it, let me
tell you, now as soon as you click,
all your sub-limits will appear there, choose any amount
and it is very easy, friends, your premium calculator will be done in a minute,
I will tell you that also later, friends, talking about mental health,
friends, under this policy,
suppose at any time anyone gets
cyberbullying or there is any other
problem and needs any sector, does
he need advice, does he have any
cycle, then friends, that
is also available under this policy, the
cost of that will also be presented here, friends, before moving ahead
First let me tell you that
I am very active on social media.
You can follow me on Facebook.
My Twitter handle is here. You can join my
Telegram group here. You will keep getting
information from
time to time about the insurance industry.
Whichever program you follow, if
you have any questions, you
can ask me by WhatsApp. If you want to write something to me, you can
also ask me by emailing me. So let's move ahead.
Now let's talk about
its explosions. So see
what are the 21 services that
you will not get clearance in these conditions. First of all let's
talk about intentional injury, that is, under
international law, it means you have done the work intentionally
and because of that there is a loss.
You knew that it would happen because of this, then
you will not be given compensation here. Pre-
existing incident means there is already a
problem going on. If you have
bought the policy later, then that old accident which is due to an
accident will not be covered.
Any physical engineer
property damage under this, if you think that this is
any physical  If someone has been injured or
property has been damaged, then there will be
no such news here because friends, this
is a cyber policy, it will work on whatever cyber crime
or hacking happens,
delete clean a lot of it, if suppose
some documents are asked from you or some
things are asked for, you did not give those
things and there has been a lot of delay from your
side, then such losses will not be taken on the file if there has been a delay,
unexplained losses, so for any losses,
when the company asks you why this happened
and you do not have any explanation for it,
you are not able to tell them
why it happened, how it happened, what happened, that
kind of loss will be taken here, non-
personal policies, non-person name means
friends, you are working for a company,
you have a company, you have
bought the policy in your name and you want that the
loss has happened to my company, it has happened
in my company's bank account, then
you will not get it, if you have bought this individual
policy, then you can do individual only care
on Play Store  You can buy this policy from any company
or any group, which is why AIIMS will
not be able to buy it, so further I will tell you
how you can buy this policy
within minutes, it is a very easy
process,
I am also giving you the link to buy it in the description,
as soon as you click there, you will
reach the buy button and from there you
can buy it within minutes, so let me
show you how to buy it,
friends, as I clicked on the link,
I have landed on this website and this is the
official website of this body, you
can open it on your mobile if you want, it is a
very easy process, friends, here
this line starts from 50 thousand and
goes up to one crore, you can buy it
as much as you need, for example,
here I am
taking it for ₹10 for you, that I cover four family
members and 10 years, the cost is
₹6500 for one year, GST is also included in this,
friends, I have told you about all the
limits  I had told you about it, so if you
view it here, you
will see all the sub-limits, see, ITF is your
cover up to 10 lakhs, cyber extraction is your
cover up to 1 lakh, Malviya
Instruction is
your cover up to 1 lakh, Reputed Nalin
Suri is your cover up to 50 thousand, according to which
transaction, your Dastak is covered,
cyber bullying is covered up to 50,000, legal
express which you can get can be up to 10 lakh
rupees, data restoration is also up
to ₹1000000, forensic audit is 10 lakh rupees
and consequential loss is up
to 10 lakh rupees, so friends, all these will be
submitted to you here, okay, so it is a
very easy way to book here,
friends, you do not have to do anything here, you have to
enter your name, I will enter Quid for now, so here
you enter your date of birth, or
enter your address here, it happened
and here if you have any address
landmark, you can enter it
Enter your email address here. What you did was
enter your mobile number here. If
you agree to the terms and conditions here,
you will
reach the payment directly. For example, you
can make payment through credit card,
debit card, net banking, yagya ki vedi
doctor. For example, if you
choose the debit card or net banking option here,
you will see many banks here. You
can select many banks from below.
Whichever bank you own,
you will ignore here. You will
go to the bank's website from here.
Make the payment here. From here you
can also download your policy. Along with this, you will
get this policy on the email ID you entered here. Same
day, friends, this is yours and it will start. So
friends, I hope
you liked this video. If you
liked this video, then don't forget to like my channel
and share this video with your friends
so that they too have the
knowledge of what cyber insurance is
and how it can benefit us.
I will meet you guys
in the next video thank you very much for watching this video
and my name is
Sachin Verma